import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet3: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Which step is NOT part of the knowledge discovery process in data mining?",
    "options": [
      "Data cleaning",
      "Data visualization",
      "Data integration",
      "Pattern evaluation"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Which branch of machine learning does clustering fall under?",
    "options": [
      "Unsupervised Learning",
      "Reinforcement Learning",
      "Supervised Learning",
      "Semi-supervised Learning"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What is another name for data mining?",
    "options": [
      "Data Cleaning",
      "Data Transformation",
      "Knowledge Discovery in Database (KDD)",
      "Data Warehousing"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Which application of data mining helps in predicting customer behavior for enhancing customer relationships?",
    "options": [
      "Market Basket Analysis",
      "Fraud Detection",
      "Customer Relationship Management",
      "Financial Banking"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "In association rule mining, what is the 'antecedent' in the rule If A then B?",
    "options": [
      "The 'If' element",
      "The 'Then' element",
      "The frequency of an itemset",
      "The ratio of transactions"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "Which algorithm uses a breadth-first search and Hash Tree to calculate the itemset efficiently?",
    "options": [
      "Eclat Algorithm",
      "F-P Growth Algorithm",
      "Apriori Algorithm",
      "Decision Tree Algorithm"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "Which clustering method divides data into non-hierarchical groups and is also known as the centroid-based method?",
    "options": [
      "Density-Based Clustering",
      "Hierarchical Clustering",
      "Partitioning Clustering",
      "Fuzzy Clustering"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "Which type of clustering allows a data object to belong to more than one cluster?",
    "options": [
      "Partitioning Clustering",
      "Density-Based Clustering",
      "Hierarchical Clustering",
      "Fuzzy Clustering"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What are the primary components of a graph in graph analytics?",
    "options": [
      "Nodes, clusters, dimensions",
      "Vertices, paths, cycles",
      "Nodes (vertices), arcs (edges), weights",
      "Degrees, cycles, connectivity"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a property of graphs?",
    "options": [
      "Degree",
      "Path",
      "Cycle",
      "Frequency"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  }
]
